Please contact turkision@gmail.com for any inquiries
No living creature was harmed during the
filming of this series.
After two days
Yenişehir
Episode 103
Wrist strength alone is not enough
to use a sword.
You must keep your
feet firmly on the ground.
Your movements are
weighed according to this.
I know, Osman Bey.
Besides, I'm not alone.
Don't think we are all alone.
We keep fighting, my Bey.
This is my pleasure.
Come and see.
Alps.
Tell me now.
Orhan.
What made you look back?
I wanted to see if there was a
warrior behind me or not, father.
I won't ignore.
Aladdin.
You tell me.
Why didn't you look behind?
You will not ask for Alps to support you
while you are training your sons.
You weren't supposed to waste my move.
You are like the fingers of one hand.
They become one fist together.
And you strike the heart of the infidels.
Who are we going to hit?
First, me.
Come here.
We will not allow you to
defeat us, Osman Bey.
Brother, fight well.
We fought well.
While you were trying to protect
yourself from the dagger...
you left your neck unprotected,father.
Mashallah!
War is a trick.
Yes.
But your dagger is useless.
Boys.
The enemy plots in this way.
But we are the ones who
will knit the biggest game.
You are ready now.
There is no use in their
traps, my Bey.
We took refuge for the good of the scheming.
Hear me well now.
Sons of the North.
Get ready...
for the black curse to embrace you.
Make offerings to Odin.
Valhalla will open the doors for you.
Black curse!
The court that will be held will
kill Öktem and his daughter.
It's all thanks to you.
My beautiful lover.
Shh, the ground will hear, lover.
Öktem raided the village.
And his daughter attacked Subasi.
What did we do?
I will join the trial.
The court's decision
will spark a civil war.
Osman will get caught between me and
the civil war, and be crushed.
This civil war will be the beginning
of realizing our dreams.
I'll take Yenişehir.
How are you going to do this while Osman
is in town?
You will see.
I will kick Osman out of the city.
I will destroy him outside.
And Yenişehir will burn
with the fire of my anger.
Kantakuzenos will only come out alive.
Why do you give Cantakosanos
so much importance?
I'm jealous.
Oh Olof.
This is the way to make my
dreams come true.
His empire
will give me all the armies of Rome.
Forget all the famous leaders you know.
History will only write
about Olof's revenge.
Osman is the beginning.
No civilization will remain that
will not be afraid of my shadow.
Soldiers!
You are...
the giant wave that destroys
empires, Olof.
Everyone is helpless in front of you, my love.
Today, you will burn Yenisehir.
Boys.
They will want to burn Yenişehir.
But we will not allow this.
It's time to test what you learned in
this training through a great war.
Our future is tied to this war of mind.
We will be one body.
And one mind.
While one of you confuse their minds...
the other will hit their bodies.
I will cut off their heads.
But boys...
The main burden will be on your shoulders.
If you aren't there, there will be no move.
If there is a mistake, there
will be no victory.
They want to hit us with our
justice, don't they, father?
Shall we allow this?
Will they be able to hit us?
They will.
They will even start a civil war.
While they think they have
achieved their goals...
the arena will be ours.
Whoever succeeds in his plan
will weaken his defenses.
Whoever loosens his defenses, his
neck will be under our swords.
Come here.
Get ready.
Come on.
The arrow has come out of
the bow, Beys.
If a death sentence is issued
by the court today...
we will go to Yenişehir and take our Bey.
I stand with you, Bengi Hatun.
We will not allow Öktem Bey to become
a victim of slander.
We are with you.
So, stay in the tribe and wait for news from me.
Let's see whether Osman Bey will believe
the words of the infidels or Öktem Bey.
Our shepherd has come.
It is clear that Malhun Hatun
was suspicious and did not stand still.
We are not a herd of sheep, Beys.
We are a pack of wolves.
You know what to do if necessary
Bengi Hatun.
Come, Turgut Bey.
You put my Bey in danger.
Come and sit.
Your coming is never a good sign.
We have no eye for
his position, Bengi Hatun.
We are here for justice.
You want to say you are
asking for our heads.
Why are you here, Uraz Bey?
And you, Şahin Bey?
What are you doing?
Let's see if you have a problem
It's a black day, Turgut Bey.
A friend must stand by you on a dark day.
Tell us why you came.
Until the court's decision...
I will stay in the tribe with my Alps.
Beware that no one thinks or
does anything until then.
Justice will decide whether
a day is black or white.
Damn your justice.
If you had justice...
you wouldn't put my husband and daughter
in the cell.
You would put infidels under the dirt.
Alps!
Prepare my horse.
We'll go to court.
Our tribe is your trust, Beys.
Wait for news from me.
Never worry, Bengi Hatun.
Your tribe and your Alps are my trust.
Go now.
Go to court.
Come on.
My gold pieces...
are going to Constantinople, huh?
Yes, my Bey.
Well, shall I leave her
love for someone else?
We will get to them at the right time.
Get behind the caravan quickly.
Let the court be held.
Let's wait for Osman's lands to be a mess.
And I will become the richest
merchant in the West and the East.
You will become, my Bey.
And you will see me too, Inshallah.
I shouldn't see you now in order
to see you then.
I put you on a mission, Hüseyin, come on.
Your command, my Bey.
Sir, you are used to
passing judgment in your tent...
and ensuring justice through tradition.
Will you be able to remain silent in court
and abide by my judgment?
What makes you suspicious?
You come from Konya.
Is Konya's justice better than us?
No, my Bey.
Every place governed by Sharia is equal.
No.
You think...
I will deviate from justice.
You think I won't remain silent
and get involved in court.
Don't worry.
I am the sword of justice.
And you are the pen of justice.
It will be under your control.
What will be fixed, will be fixed by you.
Thank you, my Bey.
And I will take revenge on the heathens.
The trial of what I do takes
place on the battlefield.
The case is yours.
I trust that you will judge with justice.
Thank you.
Thank you, my Bey.
However, don't you...
compare us to others.
We will be remembered for our
judgment of the world...
and the justice we spread to the world.
Thank you.
Come on.
Öktem.
Alçiçek.
I will save you.
I swear I will save you.
We will not succumb to slanders, mother.
What they did will not go unpunished.
You definitely won't give up.
I'll burn this city
for a single hair of yours.
Hatun.
Don't make a mistake.
Let's go
When the court is over, tell the Beys.
The arrow that came out
of the bow will pierce.
Ayşe Hatun.
Yes, Ayşe Hatun.
Ayşe Hatun, mother of Aktemur, whom
your rebellious daughter wanted to kill.
Go on your way, Hatun.
I have a lot of worries.
Look at me.
Your daughter did something wrong.
You didn't hold her rope as her mother.
Look at what you are saying
instead of asking for forgiveness.
What do you mean when you say
you didn't catch her rope, Hatun?
I don't consider my daughter a dog
as you do as I won't grab her rope. (discipline her)
Hatun.
The one you are talking
about is not only Ayşe's son...
he is the Subasi of the state.
Weigh your words, then speak.
You won't be able to take it anymore.
My back bear the pain of losing a brother.
And bear the burden of slander.
Let me decide for myself what
I'm going to say, Malhun Hatun.
Say what you want in your tribe.
But this place is my city.
Shut up if you don't want to go
to prison like the rest of your family.
The same applies to you, Ayşe Hatun.
The smell of blood.
Tell the Beys.
Today, we will not just save our Bey.
We will take revenge too.
Let them know this.
Will you excuse me, Aktemur?
Come in.
Where do you go before
your wound is healed, my Bey?
Kumral Abdad said you should rest.
Is there any news about Alçiçek?
Do not you dare!
Don't say
her name in front of your mother, my Bey.
Say it, Ülgen Hatun.
Where's Alçiçek?
Don't lose your mind..
She's brought to the palace.
To the palace?
But you didn't hear from me.
Say, where is she now?
My Bey.
Your wound hasn't healed yet.
This is not the time
for you to be stubborn.
Are you going after that girl
who tried to kill you again?
Mother.
I don't believe Alçiçek hurt me.
How did you blind your eyes?
The girl stabbed you, Aktemur.
You haven't opened your
eyes for a whole day.
What are you saying?
If the arrow got here...
Look, just one finger.
If it got here, you'd die.
Not your wound, but your funeral...
Don't make me say it!
We meet in court, mother.
Salam Alaikum.
Alaikum Salam.
Where are you coming from, Clerk?
We face the rebels.
I did my job and came.
My Alaaddin.
The trial has not started yet, what
are you writing?
I write the date...
for the trial, Malhun mother.
Mashallah.
Sit here, Ayşe Hatun.
Osman Bey's loyal soldiers.
The word "soldier" is said to your men.
We are called Alps.
No difference.
It is enough that you do
not appear in front of me.
You are not allowed to enter
Osman Bey's palace with your swords.
Let's go
Come on.
Where is Osman Bey?
My Bey comes when he wants.
Go.
Where is Kantakuzenos?
Oh, the world for which we perished...
Murderers are hosted in the palace.
Look at how Beys are treated.
Okay, then.
You should have thought about that before you ordered
your soldiers to raid my village, Öktem.
What you deserve is to be killed.
Time to go home.
Osman Bey.
We're going to court, right?
I think I've waited long enough.
You will not come to court.
What does that mean?
I'm here for that court.
- Emperor...
- You are heir to the throne.
Your first job is not to die.
That woman named Frigg and Olof...
They might try to kill you in court.
I will not give up my mission out of fear.
I'm the one who got hurt.
And what was stolen is my gold
and the village is mine.
But you are in lands.
The health of my guest matters to me.
Do not worry.
You will go to Constantinople in good
health when justice is served.
Osman Bey, this is the
last time I trust you.
When you don't trust me...
know that death will be right behind you.
Open, I have something to
ask Alçiçek Hatun.
- Subasi...
- I said open, Ayaz Alp.
Subasi.
Alçiçek.
You are fine, right?
I'm not, Alçiçek.
I did not do it.
I know.
You...
Be sure that I will let everyone
know your innocence.
You were saying me to
trust the justice of Osman Bey.
That justice is now putting the noose
on my father's neck, Subasi.
If I had a thousand necks...
I would sacrifice them all to stop the
tears in your eyes.
But I'm handcuffed
in front of justice, Alçiçek.
I'm saying my dad will die.
I say he will die without guilt, don't
you understand?
He won't die, he won't die, Alçiçek.
Trust in the justice of Osman Bey.
Don't, Alçiçek.
Don't be angry.
Don't.
Save my father, Subasi.
Save my father.
Justice will be served today.
You will live the same fate as your men
who raided my village, Öktem.
Don't worry, you dog.
Their destiny is martyrdom.
Martyrdom is a grace for us.
You will be punished.
You will drown in the blood
of the innocents you killed.
Today or tomorrow.
Aren't Osman Bey coming?
Osman Bey is coming.
Stop asking.
The court is the only
one who will ask questions today.
Where is Kantakuzenos?
Waiting for his wound to heal.
He was the target of a woman named Frigg.
For this reason, I keep
him in a safe place.
Isn't your testimony enough?
My testimony is enough to burn
the entire tribe of Öktem.
And there is an injury of
Kantakuzenos as well.
He'll be punished for doing that too.
The punishment for all this is death.
Dog!
I didn't hit Cantakozanos and I
didn't raid the village.
Every breath you take is contempt for me!
Justice will be served and
you will die, Öktem.
I will cut off your head with
my own hands.
Otherwise, I will do my justice myself.
Shut up!
This court was held for justice.
Öktem Bey.
Stop disobedience.
Shut up now.
And you will
submit your testimony.
But if you try to achieve
justice on your own...
Your head will not go to
Constantinople with your body.
- Salam Alaikum.
- Alaikum Salam.
I turn my back on the customary
laws of our traditions.
I guide my way through the
legal laws of Qur’an and I judge by them.
Our court does not stand by anyone.
It's charged with achieving justice without
regard to anyone's religion or lineage.
I'll start the trial, sit down.
A cursed incident occurred on the
3rd of the month of Safar at Akça.
The truth will come out today.
Whoever did the wrong will be punished.
Commander Olof, we're listening to you.
Öktem Bey has given an order to
kill more than 50 innocent people.
He plundered Rome's golds.
The prince Kantakuzenos
was infected in his tribe.
Only the soul can pay the
price for all these sins.
We decide this, Olof.
What's your defense, Öktem Bey?
I said it before too...
They said I raided the village.
My Alps were on a mission there.
They said gold was found in your tribe.
I don't know about any of these things.
I have complete confidence in the court.
But true justice is in the afterlife.
And there I will hold the collar
of those who sowed sedition.
Be ready, our anger awaits them.
Now, attack!
My Bey, what's going on?
Who are they?
Bayındır Bey knows good gold.
The whole world is after
what he set its sights on.
Let's let them kill each other.
- Salam Alaikum.
- Alaikum Salam.
Charges have been filed.
In order to make a decision,
the other case must be heard.
Subasi Aktemur Bey,
we are listening to you
I first tried to kill the captive.
I stood in front of her.
She stabbed me.
But not on purpose.
While she wanted to kill the
captive, I walked in between them.
I wanted to know the link between the captive
and those dogs who killed my uncle.
Don't speak before you are
allowed to speak, Alçiçek Hatun.
Alçiçek Hatun is innocent.
The guilt is committed to the
state, not to you, Aktemur Bey.
You can't make up your mind.
As long as I am the Subasi...
As long as I represent the state...
I say that this crime
was not committed against me.
She says she stuck the dagger
by mistake, what about the arrow?
If it deviated a little, you'd lose
your soul, Subasi.
Shall I command you to be
silent one by one, Ayşe Hatun?
Silence!
What do you say about the
arrow incident, Aktemur Bey?
I did not see the archer.
The only thing I know is that I was
wounded by Alçiçek Hatun's arrow.
Bala Hatun, what do you say?
When we found Aktemur injured...
We caught the Alçiçek near him.
The arrow and the bow were in the
hands of the Alçiçek, Judge Dursun.
Alçiçek Hatun.
Do you have a defense against
what is said?
As Subasi told you...
I am not the one who shot
the arrow.
Someone hit me on the head.
When I opened my eyes, the bow
was in my hand.
That liar.
You're lying.
She is lying.
It's over, Ayşe Hatun.
Get out.
Osman Bey.
Do you have anything to say?
I have not witnessed this incident.
But of course, I can not accept the
attack on the Subasi of Yenişehir...
my guest, Kantakuzenos.
There is no judgment for me in this court.
You are the decision-maker, Judge Dursun.
Alçiçek Hatun's first attack on Subasi
Aktemur Bey sets a precedent for the second.
The penalty is 5-years of exile.
However...
as the offense was committed
against Subasi...
it's considered that it
was committed against the state.
The period of exile was
increased to 10 years.
I will not allow this.
And as for Öktem Bey....
Batur Alp, who appears to be guilty...
had brought gold to the tribe.
This proves that he is acting on
orders from Öktem Bey.
Öktem Bey's hands are stained with the
blood of all those innocents.
The punishment for such a crime can
only be the death penalty.
Execution.
Thank Allah, we are believers.
Goodness comes from Allah.
And evil is from Allah.
Of course.
The court is now over.
Tradition leaves the place
when injustice enters it.
It's over, Osman Bey.
You have no justice or tradition left
Search the place, don't let
anyone breathe.
Cut off the heads of the dead.
Bring the horses.
Horses will carry the golds.
I have a more important job now.
The horse is for the one who rides it
and the sword is for the one who wears it.
That gold will not be yours.
Will my Bey leave them for the others?
Come on, let's go and tell Bayındır Bey.
I smell blood already.
Olof will have a chance for revenge.
And now it's time for me to be Frigg.
I admire your justice
very much, Osman Bey.
You haven't seen anything yet.
Speak.
My Bey, they raided the caravan that was
carrying gold to Constantinople.
Delivering the gold was my mission.
Osman Bey, I will go and find.
No.
You can not move on
my land without my knowledge.
If we're going, we'll go together.
Alps!
Get ready!
The court is over.
They will execute our Öktem Bey.
They expelled Alçiçek Hatun from her land.
It's time, Beys.
What are you doing?
The consequences of what
you're doing are big.
It signifies a civil war.
It's over, Turgut Bey.
The swords came out of their sheaths.
The knife touched the bone.
You are our captive until we rescue
Öktem Bey from that dungeon.
Do you intend to make the brothers fight?
If something like that happens,
I won't leave you unpunished.
And I will not spare you, Uraz Bey.
Arrest him.
It's time for revenge, Beys.
We'll go and rescue Öktem Bey.
Come on.
What you're doing is not right, Beys.
The enemies are not here, they
are on the border.
They are looking for
a mess.
You make Turks fight among themselves
Don't do this.
Osman is heading towards the trap.
And gold is with us
But the first victim of the
civil war will be Turgut.
Alps, look everywhere.
Don't come back before
you find a trace.
My Bey, the ones who stole the gold
are the same ones who raided the Macri.
They took the horses and
gold towards Iznik.
What your eyes have seen undoes all knots.
But we need those knots now.
It makes us earn money.
But, my Bey, the enemies are not the
ones we are used to.
We have to give them a good game.
The issue is about gold, Hüseyin.
I will plan such a game that...
Satan will come and ask us for advice.
Planning games is easy, Hüseyin.
That gold will be mine.
I won't let anyone take it.
I will not leave it to anyone.
Come on, get my horse!
From this side, Osman Bey.
Same horse traces...
But it is deeper.
They put gold on the horses...
And they went in that direction.
You're pulling us toward
a trap, aren't you?
But you will be the one who gets caught
despite knowing about the trap.
I admire your intelligence, Osman.
Yes, I set a trap for you.
But we have come to the
end of the road now.
The path of those who take the sun as a
banner and the sky as a tent doesn't end.
Judge Dursun is charged with
making a decision based on the evidence.
But those enemies who
put that evidence there...
I will find them and cut off their hands.
- Judge Dursun.
- My Bey.
What I want from you is to postpone the
execution of the sentence until I come.
Inshallah, I will find the guilty ones
and bring them.
Then, justice will be served.
Thank you, my Bey.
Thank you.
Wind!
Bring my black curse
It's over, Osman.
It's over.
The balance of your justice is spoiled.
It was not Öktem who
raided the village...
it was me.
I'm the one who shot Aktemur.
Look, you're alone.
Now I will kill you too.
And then I will burn Yenisehir.
You can't burn anything.
As for me, I will enjoy
spoiling the traps.
Turgut.
I am Aladdin, son of the Ghazi Osman Bey.
I came here by order of him.
And my words are his words.
You have to trust what
I'm going to tell you now.
Osman Bey believes Öktem Bey.
And I made a game to reveal the truth.
And I need your help.
After the trial is over, Öktem Bey
will walk towards a trap.
And he will leave his Alps in Yenişehir.
So Olof will think he has put
Osman Bey into the trap he set.
And I will go with Öktem Bey's Alps
to help Osman Bey.
To catch that dog named Olof.
Beys.
The end of those
who try to divide us...
will be
through our union together, Inshallah.
Inshallah.
And now, Beys...
are you with us?
We are with you, Aladdin Bey.
Thank you.
Orhan.
Bala.
Whoever does something, he
must bear the consequences
Come on, sisters.
Bala.
Orhan.
Surrender or...
be a Muslim and take refuge
in our justice.
Or fight.
I cursed you, Osman.
Alps!
Hit the chests of the infidels
for the sake of Allah.
O Allah!
Attack!
You dishonorable!
We'll live today for the
revenge we'll get later.
We have to go.
No, Frigg, no!
Olof, not today.
Not today, Olof.
I will kill him!
Let's go, let's go.
Withdraw!
Saruza!
Come on.
You finally demolished my tent.
But I won't leave it here.
I'll make you pay the price!
Easy, Hatun!
I'm trying to understand your pain...
but enough is enough.
My patience has limits too.
I have no patience, Hatun.
You want to execute my husband and take
my only daughter away from me.
You upset a mother.
You will never get rid of my curse.
Bengi Hatun.
You say something you'll regret later.
Don't think I'll stop.
I swear...
I will not let my husband and
daughter become your victim.
Patience!
- Mother!
- My Çiçek! (flower)
My beautiful daughter.
Why are you laughing?
What happened?
We knew Öktem Bey and
Alçiçek were innocent.
What are you saying, Malhun Hatun?
Osman Bey had trusted Öktem Bey
from the start.
In order for the truth to be revealed to all...
he's deceiving Olof.
What about the court?
The verdict? They're
building the gallows outside.
When Osman Bey reveals the truth...
the verdict of the court will
be overturned, mother.
Our innocence will be known.
When the trial is over...
the men were going to rebel.
The news will have reached them
a long time ago, Bey.
What have you done, Hatun?
What have you done?
We knew this too, Bengi Hatun.
I knew you wouldn't stand still.
You didn't trust Osman Bey...
and you didn't wait.
You listened to the devil and disobeyed.
How should I know, Malhun Hatun?
What would you do if you
were me?
If they took your husband and daughter...
I would have been patient, Hatun.
I would trust Osman Bey.
The thing you did was a civil war.
You would make brothers fight each other.
Alçiçek.
Take good care of your mother.
See what happens
if you don't control your anger.
You are right, Malhun Hatun.
Hatun acted recklessly.
Forgive her
Don't worry.
We should pray for...
...Osman Bey to throw off Olof's mask.
What if that dog doesn't rise to the bait?
What will we do then?
Are you going to walk to your death?
Give me patience, Allah.
My Bey!
Olof is running to the fortress.
What shall we do?
We know where he is.
We'll hit him when it's time.
Let's go.
Marmaracik Castle
Who are you?
Olof
Commander Olof.
Who are you running from?
I don't run away from anyone.
I am only surviving for vengeance.
I am here in the name of the emperor
Put down your spears.
Increase precautions around the castle.
Now!
Yenisehir
Come in, dear.
The good news has come, thank Allah
you are free now.
Olof confessed his all betrayals.
Certainly the day will come when
he will be punished for his actions.
Insha'Allah.
Rest assured, Bengi Hatun.
Have a rest now.
Daughter, bring me some water, will you?
Hatun!
Tell me now.
What do you think you did by
gathering the Beys and rebel?
How could you do this?
I did everything to protect you
and my daughter.
How could I know
that Osman had a game?
I trusted him and surrendered myself,
you should have trusted me too, Hatun!
But no, you just can't keep calm can you?!
I always told you to...
...keep your anger under control!
Is this all my fault now, Oktem Bey?
What are you talking about?
What if there was no game?
Should I have watched your death
while they hang you?
No!
I would do the same thing again!
You are still stubborn, Hatun!
Stop already!
You threw me, my tribe and my alps
in danger, don't you see?
- You are going too far Oktem Bey!
- Shut up!
Don't say a word.
I can die, Hatun.
But my tribe will stay!
From now on, nothing will be done
without my knowledge.
You will remember these words, Oktem Bey.
You will remember it.
You'll remember this talk when Osman
stabs you in the back again.
I'll be by your side that day too.
But when that day comes...
...I will remind you of these words
one by one, Oktem Bey.
Huseyin, you said the cavalry will
come first, you are sure, right?
Here they are, my Bey
Come to me.
Bring me my gold.
Shall we shoot arrows, my Bey?
Wait.
- Now, my Bey?
- Wait!
We should shoot now my Bey!
Right now!
Let's go Alps, their bodies belong
to the ground, their gold belongs to us.
None of you will survive!
Look at this!
Check that out, Huseyin!
They are shining like sun!
But these shine better than sun does!
Am I right, Huseyin?
Like you said, my Bey.
Come on, don't leave any trace behind.
Load the chest.
Let's go back before they
realise what happened.
Justice will be served.
As you see.
The real guilties are here.
If you want to keep your secret hidden
even from the enemy...
...you should never talk about it
to anyone, even to a friend.
This is why I didn't tell you earlier,
Oktem Bey.
Forgive us.
What can I say, Osman Bey.
We repeat the same
thing from the beginning.
I give you my blessings.
Thank you Osman Bey.
However, delayed justice is not justice.
Bengi Hatun.
It was late and difficult.
We needed to play by their rules.
What did what we had to.
Eyvallah (okay)
I give you my blessings.
Judge Dursun.
My Bey.
You always decide according to the evidence.
Here you see the real criminals.
Olof is their head.
And these are his toys.
They ended many lives.
They shall be punished.
The scales of justice weighed
the wrong side, my Bey.
After punishing these traitors,
the scales of justice will be balanced.
Olof is our enemy.
The place where he's hiding is Marmaracik.
We will not stop until we make it our land
where the enemy hides.
Alps!
I'll wait for you at my table when
the sun goes down
We will forget our pain
and remember our martyrs
We'll talk about
our new plans.
Eyvallah my Bey, Eyvallah (sure).
Give me your blessings, Oktem Bey.
You too, Judge Dursun.
I do.
Yenişehir, Osman Bey's mansion.
How dexterous you are!
Do you think I can't cook because
I'm a fighter, Ulgen Hatun?
My father loves my meals the most.
Praise be!
He must have missed your meals.
Whoever marries you
will live longer, girl!
How is it going, Hatuns?
Get out of here now!
Ayse Hatun is about to come.
She will burn us!
How is it going, Alcicek Hatun?
Thank you, Subasi.
For everything.
Slow down, slow down my Bey!
If you are too thirsty,
just toss the whole bottle.
You were right, Subasi.
Osman Bey was always with us.
Now it's all over.
Don't think about this anymore.
How is your wound, Subasi?
So will you keep calling me Subasi,
Cicek Hatun?
My name is Alcicek, Subasi!
You still do it.
Aktemur!
Are you still hovering around my son?
Mother!
The truth came out.
Alcicek is innocent.
- Stop it.
- Stop what?
Didn't this girl stab you?
How can you still
look at this young man's face?
Don't you ever feel guilty?
I...
It was an accident.
Satan was also innocent before
he turned into Satan.
You will only cause misfortune for my son.
Stay away from my son.
I am telling you that's enough, mother!
You are going too far!
Didn't I tell you not to see this girl again?
The more...
The more I let you,
the further you go, mother!
Aktemur!
Leave it, leave it.
This wound will revive my vengeance.
Don't tie it up, it will bleed and heal.
I swear to you, I will make Osman's
head a banner over this castle.
We'll do it together.
We'll do it together darling.
Bad news!
The men I gave the gold
were ambushed.
What about the gold?
They stole the gold and
killed our men, Olof.
No! No!
Osman Bey.
If you continue to keep me a prisoner,
I will consider it a reason for war.
Is this how you react to the man
who saved your life?
Olof came to the court today.
He was constantly asking about you.
And set a trap on the way to Yenisehir.
You were the target.
I shielded you from his wrath.
And what about the court?
Oktem Bey has been acquitted.
Olof is the one who set the whole game.
Why would Olof do something like this?
I don't want to hear your lies anymore.
You'll believe me when he ambushes you.
You became his enemy when he found out
that you tried to accuse him.
Why would you still not believe me?
Don't be surprised, Kantakuzenos.
Do not be surprised.
Are you sure of this?
He is the one who came to my land.
He's the one who collaborated
with Frigg and Ophelia.
He and Frigg were even fighting shoulder
to shoulder today.
I must tell this to the Emperor at onceç
I know.
And tell him that my Beys are innocent.
Tell my friend Andrinakos that...
He has three days to give me Olof's head.
Otherwise, the friendship will end.
I will not be responsible for what happens.
I came here for peace, Osman Bey.
I will do whatever it takes
Of course you will.
Otherwise, you will be run over
under Turks' horses.
Rome is neither too small to be run over
under your horses...
...nor this is necessary.
Excuse me.
Have a good travel.
Do you think the truth will come out
when he arrives in Constantinople?
There are two possibilities.
If he gives us Olof's head in three days...
...this means that Kantakuzenos is innocent.
But if he does not...
...I will bury them both in the same grave.
Whether he worked with Olof or not,
we see the poison in him Osman Bey.
He's looking for someone to bite.
We carry our weapons to crush
the heads of those snakes.
Let him try.
Eyvallah.
Why did we stop, princess?
What's my job here, Sarkis?
What if they kill my father, Sarkis?
I should not have left Konstantinople.
I needed to stay and fight!
If that wasn't the only solution...
...I would have done everything to stay,
princess.
However, we just couldn't get into a war
in which we will lose.
Besides, your father would be
on the other side.
Atttack!
Sarkis!
Hang on princess.
Ride the horse and run away, princess!
I won't go without you Sarkis.
Ride the horse, princess.
You stupid!
Aims like a stupid!
I'll do it myself!
To the horses, run!
Princess!
Princess, hold on!
We're about to get rid of them.
I can't go on any longer Sarkis.
We have to keep going, princess.
I promise I will save you.
Come on princess.
Come on! Come on!
Catch them!
Faster!
You'll find out who did this, Frigg.
You will find the ones who stole my gold
and pull my wrath towards themselves.
You will find them.
So that I'll tear them apart.
No.
Odin left me in the middle of the road.
Now I will walk with the devil!
The devil has come, Olof!
My brother from another mother.
Who wouldn't want a demon brother
while fighting Osman?
I will begin the great war when I
reach Constantinople.
About time!
First they captured me
And then they attacked Marmaracik.
And the heroic leader Olof...
...repelled that attack.
So Emperor's huge army will
attack Osman.
- Hold on Princess.
- Sarkis.
Sarkis.
You will be fine, princess.
You'll be fine.
We'll get out of here.
My Bey, we have been attacked.
We are in the mine in Saraga.
Go!
Come on princess.
We must cauterize your wound.
Hold on.
Search around.
Stop it!
Foolish.
You think Osman Bey will save you?
If Osman is coming here...
Olof will definitely want to to catch him.
Go tell Olof right now.
We are here.
We'll wait by the cave, hurry up!
If an Alp did what you did...
...I would derank him and exile him.
But you are my blood.
Someone from us...
...should never fall into such a negligence.
You are my brother's trophy.
This mission is what
your father left for you.
Aktemur.
Don't you dare.
There is no forgiveness for the mistake
I did.
I neglected my job.
My Bey.
Cancel my title Subasi.
Come here.
And now you're hiding behind your mistake
and giving up your title?
Aktemur!
I did not remove your title.
Is your wound bandaged?
That wound can be bandaged.
But the wound caused by disappointing you...
I'm not talking about that wound.
I'm talking about the wound in your heart.
That wound...
That wound is deep.
So is love.
If it wasn't love...
...you wouldn't do such a mistake.
Does she love you too?
Tell me.
I don't know uncle.
You should know, you should.
You should know it when you
look at her in the eye.
So make yourself sure
and inform me.
Then we will ask her for marriage.
Do not forget that the slap was for
your negligence.
Don't make this mistake again.
That wound on your shoulder...
It will be the wound of your love that
you'll never forget for the rest of your life
I will never forget any of them, my Bey.
Any of them.
Why do you always come to my mind, Subasi?
How is it going, Alcicek Hatun.
Thank you.
Do you have a problem?
You look so distracted.
You say no, but..
But your eyes say something
else, Alcicek Hatun.
Do you know what your eyes remind me of?
In the tribe I was born in,
I used to wake up before everyone else.
I would go to hunting.
The green herbs...
And the leaves on the trees...
They all had dew drops on
them in the morning.
Look, it's just like your eyes
Dew drops are beautiful
on the leaves and herbs.
...beautiful but...
If it is because of the sadness...
...for every drop of dew...
...I'll burn the whole forest.
Come on, tell me.
What is the thing that tears your eyes?
Let me heal it.
These are tears of joy.
Thank Allah.
My father and I have been proven innocent.
Troubled times have passed.
I hope your eyes never shed
tears of sadness, Alcicek Hatun.
Always have tears of joy.
Excuse me, Uncle Bayindir.
I am in a hurry.
Constantinople
Emperor's Palace
They killed the soldiers!
And they took our gold!
And now they attacked Marmaracik, huh?
Fortunately the hero Olof was there.
He repelled the attack.
How dare Osman do this?
How dare he poison me with my daughter!?
How dare he comes in my palace
and saves me?
How dare he captures you?
Your weakness.
Because of your weakness, Emperor.
He became the hero for you
after he saved you.
He took everything he wanted.
You are the one who gave him this courage.
Emperor.
I beg you not to be weak.
Kill those who got you into this trap.
Rome has this power.
Rome has never been so small!
It won't get any smaller!
Kantakuzenos.
Send your soldiers to Olof.
And kill Ophelia whose blood is my blood!
Immediately!
Marmaracik Castle
You all.
Don't you take off your shields even inside
the walls, Commander Olof?
Moreover...
While eating.
I sleep in the armor.
Commander, Remus!
You can't know when the enemy
stabs you.
Why are you here?
Is this a question to ask a guest?
How long will I host you?
Until we erase Osman.
Only the brave deserve to live!
Are you brave?
As long as this coward is on your head...
You will not be brave!
Osman knocks on your doors!
And you're sitting here useless!
But you will also be brave, my brothers!
I'm not your enemy!
I am your new leader.
Now put your swords in their sheaths.
You will need it when Osman comes.
And you will be brave, brother.
Olof is an obedient leader of Rome.
From now on...
You are under his command.
Loyalty is measured by the wisdom
you display in front of your enemy.
Death to the enemies of Rome!
One of those kidnapped Ophelia...
and you know him.
He hasn't spoken yet.
But he will speak.
I personally will make him speak.
They found Ophelia.
I'll go and kill her.
Commander Remus, wait for me here.
Yenisehir
The fog has dissipated.
We beat our enemies.
Thank Allah my father!
Now tell me!
What lesson did you take from
what happened today?
The enemy does not fight
only with weapons, my Bey.
They spread sedition and immorality.
But the one who has the will
and maintains the unity...
He wins all the battle.
You cannot tell which side
your enemy is on.
For this reason,
our eyes should always be open.
As you should know, father, that...
Whether the sheath is full or empty.
Praise be!
You should always be like this as one body.
If one of you catches something,
the other will shoot.
You will so that
before the oppressor raises his head...
...you'll cut their breath.
But it is not enough just to hit the enemy.
The union inside must be maintained too.
And the biggest enemy...
....is sedition.
As long as we don't give it a chance
to occur...
...The blessed Islamic call
will last forever.
Who is spreading sedition, father?
Satan spreads it, my daughter.
Satan.
That Satan sows the seeds of
hypocrisy among brothers.
It separates them from each other.
They have to hold on to the rope of Allah.
They need to secure each other's back.
But they usually fall into oblivion.
And they remain naked
in front of the arrows of the enemy.
But as long as we are united...
..we will revive the cause of exalting
the word of Allah forever.
Praise be to Allah, our children
carry the love of Islam in their heart.
They are willing to put
up with anything for this.
Our dawah will spread like an arrow
through our children and grandchildren.
And we will become more powerful
than the mountains, Inshallah!
Insha'Allah.
- Brother, are you hungry?
- Like a wolf, brother!
I'm hungry too!
Let's go to the kitchen then.
I wanted such a supper from Ulgen Hatun!
Are we eating liver today, brother?
- There must be halva too, right?
- Yes.
First one to go to the kitchen
eats two plates of halva!
Let's go brother.
Cerkutay Alp!
Oh man!
Did you eat it all?
I gave him three plates of meal
to protect your food from him!
He is never full.
Cerkutay Alp.
How will we wake him up?
He does not hear us.
He eats our food and does not hear us!
What will we eat now?
Wait a minute! We should teach
Cerkutay Alp a lesson.
We should also open his ears!
Shouldn't we, Fatima?
I'll be right back.
- What are you doing Ulgen Hatun?
- Desperate diseases have desperate remedies.
Only drums can open Cerkutay Alp's ears!
Come on, each of you grab a plate,
bowl, or whatever you can find!
Are you ready?
Come on, come on, valiants!
Attack, my Bey!
My Bey!
What are you doing?
We were playing my new song.
Its name is "you don't hear".
You don't hear?
Do you hear us?
Oh did it work?
Do you hear me?
I don't hear you, I don't hear you!
I don't hear, I don't hear, I don't hear you!
No my Bey, I don't hear you!
Cerkutay doesn't hear!
He doesn't hear!
No, I wo... I don't hear!
Cerkutay doesn't hear!
In the name of of Allah
the Merciful, the Compassionate.
Enjoy it.
In the name of Allah.
Here, daughter.
Justice has been served
thanks to you, Osman Bey.
And despite what we lived, you host
us at your table, may Allah bless you.
We couldn't realise the big picture.
We disobeyed, we are sorry Osman Bey.
When it comes to children,
the eyes of mothers goes blind.
I ignore what you did,
considering that you are a mother.
Your tribe has been through
a difficult test.
You must not be led by your anger
and make such a mistake again.
There is justice in these lands.
No one should attempt to
achieve justice on their own.
Isn't that right, my daughter, Alcicek?
Just like you said, Osman Bey.
Allah bless you.
You stood by us in this
difficult situation and supported us.
Challanges are not over yet.
We are after a huge case.
There will be many difficult challanges
in the way of this dawah.
We have to trust each other
and support each other.
We will support each other so that...
We can build a strong country together.
Let's finish our meals first, Oktem Bey,
and then I'll have a talk with you.
Eyvallah my Bey.
My Bey.
Allow me to check on my mother.
Who are you, knocking like a payee?
Do you know what time is it?
Give me the cloth the Beys wear.
We don't work at this hour.
Come tomorrow, please.
Aren't you the best seller here,
Hatun?
I am.
I think you should not
miss the opportunity.
Give me of the finest fabrics,
and I will shower you with gold.
Let me see the gold first.
I need to see if it is worth
waking me up from my sleep.
You must be very rich.
Why do you ask?
Just mind your gold!
Here, a fabric for me!
Prepare it by tomorrow.
I'll come and pick it up.
Consider it done.
We have found the trail of the spy of
Osman and Ophelia.
And I think I found the gold.
Will you carry me through
the Sirat Bridge?
It's like you showered in the
rivers of paradise.
We couldn't catch, my Bey.
Looks like you've come from
a very tough road.
From far away.
You're coming from overseas.
It seems you are angry.
But its not because of the
distance of the way.
You stumbled.
You dropped your load.
Do you still have anything to carry?
What is that, Kumral Abdal?
You're Konuralp's horse!
Oh Allah, protect him.
Inform my Bey at once!
- Oguz Alp, give water to the horse.
- Yes my Bey.
Hurry up get the water, hurry up!
All those valiants died for something.
They died for our dawah.
But I told you when I gave you
the location of the black tree.
It's next door to Macri and
we would conquer there too.
Yes my Bey, you told me that
You've gone through a lot, Oktem Bey.
But it's all worth it.
The road is tough and we
already need a tough Bey.
You have been very patient,
may Allah bless you.
The one who shoots in hurry
misses the greater prays, my Bey.
I fought for many years in these lands.
I have buried many valiants.
Yet I still haven't tasted the martyrdom.
This path taught us about patience, my Bey.
This road will take us to Marmaracik.
It will also be difficult,
but we will be patient
- Our job has never been easy.
- Yes.
Can I come in my Bey?
Come!
Excuse us, Oktem Bey.
Eyvallah my Bey.
Tell me.
My Bey.
Konur and Ophelia are caught
in a trap while coming to Yenişehir.
They are asking for help
They are in Saraca, they are hiding
in the mine there.
Aktemur, keep the control of Yenisehir.
I'll go with the alps.
Your command, my Bey.
Ayse Hatun looked very well.
When did she get so sick that she can't
come to the dining table?
Isn't it time to end this tension
between you two, Bengi Hatun?
And look, the good and the bad
have turned out.
Am I the only one causing the tension,
Bala Hatun?
She humiliated my daughter
in the middle of the market!
You're right Bengi Hatun,
but we also know what you did too.
You must apologise to Ayse Hatun.
Why?
I spoke what needed to be spoken.
I don't regret my words.
Look, I'm here, but she doesn't dare to
appear in front of me.
Who are you to question my courage?
Maybe I just don't want to
get involved with dirt.
Hatuns, come back to your senses!
Ayse Hatun.
Bengi Hatun is our guest.
Be silent.
You raised a very spoiled son, Hautn.
She stabbed him, so what?
He didn't die.
- You...
- Ayse!
Bengi Hatun.
Watch your words!
Both are our children!
This issue is now closed!
Excuse me.
You humiliated me to the world of Turks!
I will divide this mansion into two
seperate pieces!
I came to get your liver out of your mouth!
Osman's mouse!
Osman?
What does he mean, Sarkis?
Didn't he tell you his real name?
He was going to take you to Osman Bey,
wasn't he?
Osman's loyal spy.
Did you deceive me too, Sarkis?
- I'll tell you everything, princess.
- You won't be able to.
You won't have a head left to speak.
Infidel!
Come.
Stop!
You want me! Take me!
We already have you, princess.
Take her to Marmaracik.
I will wait for Osman.
- No leave me!
- I will be your hell, Olof!
Let go of me!
Sarkis! Sarkis!
You trust Osman Bey, don't you?
He will come and save you from here.
You're wondering why
I didn't kill you, right?
Live until he comes,
because you will kill Osman.
Yes Malhun Hatun, I am listening to you.
Alcicek, I'll ask this once and directly.
You know Aktemur is in love with you,
don't you?
What is this about, Malhun Hatun?
Don't you know?
Did you not understand looking
him in the eye...
...while even I realised it
watching you for once from a distance?
No.
I didn't realise.
Also, what do I have to do with this?
I was sad because
I accidentally stabbed him.
Will I love him because
I grieved and regretted?
I saw you both in the market today,
and you didn't seem like what you say.
You assessed it the
wrong way, Malhun Hatun.
I am not in love with
Aktemur or anyone else.
Brother!
Konur!
Hold this.
Brother!
Hold on a little more!
Marmaracik Castle
I don't like crying girls, princess.
I hate princesses.
I hate creatures like you.
Do you hate your beloved father too?
Is that why you tried to kill the emperor?
You have no advantage but being a princess.
And you can't fight.
The day you tried to kill your fathe...
...you gave up being a princess too
You will die being a traitor before
you can explain yourself.
This is very sad.
Do not tire yourself.
- My Bey.
- This will pass, hang on.
Alps!
Hang on.
Hang on, hang on.
My Bey.
Brother!
Hang on
Alps!
Please contact turkision@gmail.com for any inquiries